Quick and spontaneous video today because it's launch day of the new Paradise collection and it's an all black collection
So I'm super happy because I love black and of course I wanted to show you today
So get your hands on them use my discount code and I will create four different looks with the four different leggings. Let's start
guitar solo
We all fly through the night, ride or die
First look with the most outstanding, optical outstanding leggings with the chest pattern here.
I made a poll on my Instagram story and asked what's your favorite and this was the first place.
I paired it with some PVC heels top and shrug because these are the shiniest of the four
and I thought let's create a fetishy look for these and I think it looks really cool
and also with a lot of light and all the reflections. There's a lot going on with these.
For me this is like a classic goth outfit. I would go partying like this especially with my
belt. I love to combine it with leggings and yeah the truck's also nice. Not too cold. By the way
our central heating system doesn't work so today I'm freezing here in my studio.
Okay, let's try this without the shrug.
But now something's missing here, so I need a PVC choker to go with the flow here.
all right I don't know which version I prefer I like this one too without the
truck and with the choker here I think it's a bit more playful not as strict
and depending on the temperature outside I would probably rather go without the
Let's get dressed for the next look
don't know when don't know when we'll meet again
suddenly it's too late it's over now
suddenly it's too late it's over now it's over now
A super cute daytime outfit because this is what I would wear on like a chill festival day
or any kind of city day because it's so comfy. I'm wearing my demonia heels and these are like
the most comfortable heels ever. I've worn them on so many festivals, so many concerts.
my feet never hurt in them and the leggings is super comfy as well and then just a cute tank top
this one is from Amphifestival by the way see you there this year in Cologne and yeah I have to say
I was really really skeptical in the beginning with the Black Panther leggings because I was like
animal print I don't know not so sure but with this look I kind of like it I mean I had a bit
of a hard time thinking about a combination for the leggings because with the with the pattern
it's hard to find something I think other than some plain top so I opted for just one big print
here and I think it works together because this is really toned down in the
end and yeah it's just a nice black copy if you don't look too closely I want to
try it with a leather jacket because it's my go-to option and because
sometimes it's cold
Also good, but I think I like it without a jacket better.
And these pants are not as reflective and light sensitive as the first pants were.
So they're like more black.
I really feel cute in this one.
And the leggings give me some kind of steel panther, 80s hair metal vibe.
Which is kind of nice.
I would never wear any mill print in like colors, but the black one I'm surprised I like it that much anyway, let's
Do the next outfit
These pants are called Disco Ball because of the teeny tiny dots everywhere.
so I paired it with my disco ball choker which is basically a disco ball itself
and some heels and a bodysuit and to be honest this was amongst my favorites
before I tried them on now I do have to say I kind of like the Black Panther
better and I'm surprising myself by saying that I don't know but I like this
one too I mean they're all black so these are my kinds of pants I love this
collection I feel they're a bit more elegant with the pattern whereas the
other ones were a bit more playful I don't know just my opinion in general I
I do love that all of our pants have a zipper because I prefer the zipper versions.
And as with every Paradise pants we have the side seam here, the curved one, which makes a great leg and also a 3D booty.
And I just, I don't know, I barely own normal pants anymore or even jeans.
Mostly I just wear Paradise pants.
because they're comfy and I love the black gray and darker tone ones so
definitely can recommend them if you want to go shopping at paradise use my
code Celine for 10% off on the whole paradise product range I will put
everything down in the description text of course I do have one last pair and
I'm going to change now
Take my soul, my blood, my words
Let it be right or die
last look and last leggings camouflage the camouflage one made last place at my instagram
story poll so i've shown them basically in the order they were ranked on instagram
but I have to say this is my favorite one and I will grade this one which made first place on
Instagram last place because it's just I like the other styles more I'm just not the overly
patterned shiny type but this one is nice and also the Black Panther was nice because it was
really dark and this one's also not as reflective which I like it's kind of
like the gothy leggings, the black pantier and the tis one so I would definitely not
rate this last place I love the pattern I still think it's one of my favorites
now that I've seen it all myself and worn because I didn't try them on before
it's not a classic camouflage pattern just more like kind of brushstrokes like
when I do Photoshop and dry brushes that reminds me of the pattern paired it with
my Norway designs belt and necklace because they just work so well together
and that belt is just one of my favorite accessories ever and I have to point out
again wearing my bra on top of the mesh shirt I did it already once before and
I'm going to do it again because I think it's a fun way to wear things why not
wear the bra on top of the shirt because it's get a bit confused but when you
close to you think okay doesn't look weird looks good my opinion I mean of
course you can pair all of them just with a plain black t-shirt but I wanted
to show you like four different looks and yeah you can tell me in the comment
which one was your favorite I think overall my favorite look was the one with
the black panther leggings and the Amphi top and the comfy heels because it was just
cute and comfy followed by this look anyway I hope you liked this video and
happy release day to paradise if you want to see more of paradise leggings on
my channel I have a bunch of videos bunch of different colored leggings PVC
as well or thermal version shorts so check out the paradise webshop and use
my discount code everything is linked down below subscribe to my channel and
leave a thumbs up for this video you can also consider checking out my patreon
for more behind the scenes stuff and I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye